<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Five_books_of_the_genre_fiction</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling1">Fahrenheit 451</string>
    <string name="text_1">
        "Fahrenheit 451 is a dystopian novel by Ray Bradbury published in 1953. "
        "It is regarded as one of his best works.\n\n"
        "The novel presents a future American society where books are outlawed and "firemen" burn any that are found.\n"
        "The title refers to the temperature that Bradbury asserted to be the autoignition temperature of paper.\n"
        "(In reality, scientists place the autoignition temperature of paper anywhere from high 440 degrees "
        "Fahrenheit to some 30 degrees hotter, depending on the study and type of paper.)\n"
        "The novel has been the subject of interpretations focusing on the historical role of book burning in suppressing dissenting ideas.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling2">The Lord of the Rings</string>
    <string name="text_2">
        "The Lord of the Rings is an epic high-fantasy novel written by English author J. R. R. Tolkien.\n\n"
        "The story began as a sequel to Tolkien's 1937 fantasy novel The Hobbit, but eventually developed into a much larger work.\n"
        "Written in stages between 1937 and 1949, The Lord of the Rings is the best-selling novel ever written, with over 150 million copies sold.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling3">A Song of Ice and Fire</string>
    <string name="text_3">
        "A Song of Ice and Fire is a series of epic fantasy novels by the American novelist and screenwriter George R. R. Martin.\n\n" 
        "The first volume of the series, A Game of Thrones, was begun in 1991 and first published in 1996.\n"
        "Martin, who initially envisioned the series to be a trilogy, has published five out of a planned seven volumes.\n"
        "The fifth and most recent volume of the series published in 2011, A Dance with Dragons, took Martin five years to write. "
        "The sixth novel, The Winds of Winter, is still being written though is expected to be released in 2016.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling4">Nineteen Eighty-Four</string>
    <string name="text_4">
        "Nineteen Eighty-Four, often published as 1984, is a dystopian novel by English author George Orwell published in 1949.\n\n"
        "The novel is set in Airstrip One (formerly known as Great Britain), a province of the superstate Oceania in a world of perpetual war, "
        "omnipresent government surveillance and public manipulation, dictated by a political system euphemistically named English Socialism "
        "(or Ingsoc in the government's invented language, Newspeak) under the control of a privileged elite of the Inner Party, "
        "that persecutes individualism and independent thinking as thoughtcrime.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling5">The Chronicles of Narnia</string>
    <string name="text_5">
        "The Chronicles of Narnia is a series of seven high fantasy novels by author C. S. Lewis.\n\n"
        "It is considered a classic of children's literature and is the author's best-known work, having sold over 100 million copies in 47 languages.\n"
        "Written by Lewis, illustrated by Pauline Baynes, and originally published in London between 1950 and 1956, "
        "The Chronicles of Narnia has been adapted several times, complete or in part, for radio, television, the stage, and film.\n"
    </string>
</resources>
